



Mikhailov Alexey

Male, 34 years old, born on 7 July 1986

+7 (916) 1806167 alex.mikhailov@yahoo.com — preferred means of communication

Reside in: Moscow

Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia Not ready to relocate, ready for rare business trips

Desired position and salary

UX/UI Designer, Scrum Product Owner

Marketing, Advertising, PR

- Designer
- Product Manager

Employment: project work, part time, full time

Work schedule: remote working Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 10 years 3 months

August 2018 — September 2019 1 year 2 months

BetO

UX/UI designer, SCRUM product owner

UX/UI Design of Web, iOS, Android, PWA applications, and game interfaces. Managing a team of developers, testers, etc. Implementation of Agile and Scrum methodologies. Conducting hackathons and presentations for stakeholders. Conducting usability testing.

February 2012 — August 2018 6 years 7 months

MCT

Moscow, mstlab24.ru/

UX/UI designer, SCRUM product owner

UX/UI Design of the SaaS. Managing the development team. SCRUM Product Owner.

July 2006 — January 2009 2 years 7 months

1C

Disigner-illustrator

Design and illustrating the computer game interface elements.

Education

Higher

2014 Sholokhov Moscow State University for Humanities

Master of Visual Arts

2012 Stanford University

Human Computer Interaction online course, UX

2005 Tomsk State University of Architecture and Building

Architect

2017 Professional Scrum Product Owner at Unusual Concepts (Scrum.org)

Unusual Concepts, Professional Scrum Product Owner

2012 Human-Computer Interaction

Stanford University

2012 Design: Creation of Artifacts in Society

University of Pennsylvania

Tests, examinations

²⁰¹⁷ Scrum.org

Scrum.org, Professional Scrum Product Owner

Electronic certificates

2017 Professional Scrum Product Owner

Key skills

Languages Russian — Native

English — C1 — Advanced

Skills Scrum, Lean and Agile methodology UX web and mobile analytics

Sketch, Figma, Zeplin, Adobe

Further information

About me

500+ apps screens carefully designed. I have several years experience of creating and managing IT projects — mobile games, mobile applications, internet marketplaces, cloud services. High level of communication skills, ability to work as part of a team, advanced level speaking and writing english.

Key skills:

- Scrum, Lean and Agile methodology;
- UX web and mobile analytics;
- Sketch, Figma, Zeplin, Adobe;
- Expert in marketplace prototype and design;
- Return on Investment (ROI) Calculation;
- MVP planning and prototyping;
- Determining product value using Impact Mapping;
- Product Backlog management;
- Business model canvas adjustments;
- Android Material Design, iOS guidelines;
- Advanced English level.